nsmb.com 2016-12-06

# Privacy Policy - NSMB.com

#####  Words by [](). Photos by [](). Video by [](). Posted by 

#### **North Shore Interactive Solutions Statement of Privacy**

To protect your privacy, northshoremountainbiking.com and nsmb.com follows principles in accordance with worldwide practices for customer privacy and data protection.

#### **PRINCIPLE 1 — NOTICE**

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (Personal Information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you are entering a contest or ordering e-mail newsletters. We use your Personal Information for two primary purposes:

  * To alert you to product news, special offers, updated information and other new services from NorthShoreMountainBiking.com.
  * To provide our sponsors with value when contributing prizes for our competitions and prize draws.

#### **PRINCIPLE 2 – CONSENT**

northshoremountainbiking.com and nsmb.com only ever allows other companies to use our registered customers information, if they are the sponsor of a competition or prize draw and only the information received from that competition or prize draw is passed on to this sponsor. If you do not want your personal information passed on to our competition and prize draw sponsors please do not enter any competitions or prize draws on this site.

#### **PRINCIPLE 3 – SECURITY**

northshoremountainbiking.com and nsmb.com strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

#### **PRINCIPLE 4 – ENFORCEMENT**

If for some reason you believe northshoremountainbiking.com or nsmb.com has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail at admin@nsmb.com, and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Be certain the words Privacy Policy are in the Subject line.

#### **NOTICE TO PARENTS**

Parents or guardians: we want to help you guard your children’s privacy. We encourage you to talk to your children about safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet.

North Shore Interactive Solutions, Ltd. reserves the right to make changes to the privacy policy without notice to the User.

If you have any concerns or questions about North Shore Interactive Solutions’ privacy practices, please contact us at admin@nsmb.com.

“We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain  
anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use  
non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information,  
browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled  
over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide  
advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to  
you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to  
collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising  
practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit  
http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.”
